### Buy Now & Pay Later!

Icebox.com is offering service through Klarna, Affirm or Afterpay.

Add items to your cart and get approved during the checkout process!

Approvals are fast and items are paid for instantly after your approval.

### Why To Use Service?

No Credit Score Impact Quick & Easy To Follow Personal Installments Plan

[](javascript:void(0);)[Our Locations](https://www.icebox.com/locations)[](javascript:void(0);)

[0](javascript:void(0);)

 Search

By Brand

Privacy Policy
--------------

Explains what information we collect and why, how we use it, and how to review and update it.

* #### General
    
* 1.1 [www.icebox.com](https://icebox.com/) (“We”, “Our”, “Us”) is committed to the protection of personal information provided by the users (“You”, “Your”, “User”) Your agreement implies Your consent to the collection, retention and use of Your personal information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”).
* 1.2 We take the privacy of our Users seriously. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of Our users while providing a personalized and valuable service.
* 1.3 When You use the Website, the Website may collect Your device number and other personal information. A high standard of security is maintained by Us for Our users. However, the transmission of information via the internet or telephone networks is not completely secure. While We do Our best to protect Your information, particularly with respect to protection of Your personal data, www.icebox.com cannot ensure the security of Your data transmitted via the internet, telephone or any other networks.
* 1.4 Access to the contents available through the Website is conditional upon Your acceptance of this Privacy Policy which should be read together with the Terms of Use.
* 1.5 If You do not agree to any of the provisions of this Privacy Policy or Terms of Use, You should not use the Website. We may revise, alter, add, amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this Privacy Policy. By browsing, accessing and/or using this Website, You agree to be bound by any such alteration, amendment, addition or modification.  

* #### Information Collected
    
* 2.1 Information You Provide Us: In the course of using the Website, we may ask you to provide us with certain information, including contact information, such as Your name or email address, unique identifiers, such as Your user id, or similar information.  
    
* 2.2 Site Usage Information: We may receive and store certain types of internet usage information whenever You visit the Website, such as Your click-stream data and your IP address. See “IP Addresses and Click Stream Data” section below  
    
* 2.3 Email Communications: When You open emails from Us, we may receive a confirmation noting You opened the email, if Your computer supports such capabilities. We also may keep track of what emails We send You and what emails you may be receiving from Our subsidiaries and affiliates. Additionally, We keep a record of what communications You have opted to receive or not to receive.  

* #### How Information may be collected
    
* 3.1 Registration: You may be asked to complete a registration form and provide personally identifiable information; you may also be asked to choose a user ID and password in order to take advantage of certain features the Website may choose to offer, such as newsletters or contests. Participation in registration is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website.  
    
* 3.2 IP Addresses and Click-Stream Data: We may collect IP addresses and/or clickstream data. An IP address is a number associated with the service through which You access the Internet. Standing alone, Your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, We also use IP addresses for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to Our advertisers and sponsors. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information. Click-stream data is information collected by Our computers when You request web pages from the Website. Clickstream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personal information. When analyzed, this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at the Website, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.  

* #### Disclosure of Personal Information
    
* 4.1 We do not disclose Your Personal Information to any third parties other than as may be required by Us, www.icebox.com’s affiliates, partners, trusted business networks, in compliance with our Privacy Policy for the purpose of moderating the content of the Website, enhancing Your user experience, providing You personalised content and to enable Us and Our partners to provide You with targeted information which may be of benefit to you.  
    
* 4.2 Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology  
    
* 4.3 To enhance customer experience and to provide focused support, We may share generic aggregated demographic information which may include Your information collected by Us but not linked to any personally identifiable information regarding visitors and users with Our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.  
    
* 4.4 At times We are required by law or litigation to disclose personal information about the users. We may also disclose information about the User if We determine that disclosure of information is necessary for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance.  
    
* 4.5 We use Our best efforts to use information in aggregate form (so that no individual User is identified) for the following purposes:  
    
* 4.5.1 To build up marketing profiles;  
    
* 4.5.1 To aid strategic development, data collection and business analytics;  
    
* 4.5.1 To manage our relationship with advertisers and partners;  
    
* 4.5.1 To audit usage of the Website and Our mobile application; and  
    
* 4.5.1 To enhance user experience in relation to the Website (“collectively, “Permitted Use”).  
    
* 4.5 We use Our best efforts to use information in aggregate form (so that no individual User is identified) for the following purposes:  

* #### Cookies
    
* 5.1 Whenever You access the Website, We may place "cookies" on Your hard drive for record-keeping purposes to enhance Your experience or sometimes to personalize Your experience. Cookies are small text files that are placed on Your computer’s hard drive by the websites You visit. Cookies help Us to identify information relating Your activities and to retain information relating to Your preferences and history on the Website.  
    
* 5.2 Ad targeting cookies: We and/or Our service providers may use advertising cookies to deliver ads that are more relevant to You and Your interests.  
    
* 5.3 You may choose to disable cookies by turning off cookie feature on the web browser. However, by disabling this feature, some parts of the Website may not function properly. This may prevent You from taking full advantage of the Website.  

* #### Confidentiality
    
* 6.1Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, We will keep Your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless We believe in good faith that disclosure of Your Personal Information or any other information We collect about You is necessary for Permitted Use or to:  
    
* 6.1.1Comply with a court order or other legal process;  
    
* 6.1.2 Protect the rights, property or safety of [www.icebox.com](#) or another party;  
    
* 6.1.3 Enforce the policy or any agreement, including Terms of Use; or  
    
* 6.1.4 Respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties.  

* #### Security
    
* 7.1The security of Your Personal Information is important to Us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to Us, both during transmission and once We receive it  
    
* 7.2Although We make best possible efforts to store Personal Information in a secure operating environment that is not open to the public, You should understand that there is no such thing as complete security, and We do not guarantee that there will be no unintended disclosures of Your Personal Information. If We become aware that Your Personal Information has been disclosed in a manner not in accordance with this Privacy Policy, We will use reasonable efforts to notify You of the nature and extent of such disclosure (to the extent We know that information) as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law.  

* #### Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy
    
* We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy so please review it frequently. In all cases, use of information We collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. You hereby acknowledge and agree that it is Your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of the modifications. If You disagree to any of the changes to the Privacy Policy, You shall refrain from using or accessing the Website. Your continued use of the Website, following the posting of the revised Policy shall indicate Your acceptance and acknowledgement of the changes and You will be bound by it.  

* #### Updates and Changes to Your Personal Information  
    
* You have a right to correct any errors in Your Personal Information available with Us. You may request Us in writing that We cease to use Your Personal Information. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.  

* #### International Users  
    
* Please note that the Website is directed towards users who reside in the United States. By using the Website, You consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of Your information in and to the United States, or other countries and territories, pursuant to the laws of the United States. While some of these countries may not offer the same level of privacy protection as Your own, We commit to uphold the privacy protections as explained in this privacy policy.  

* #### Contact Us  
    
* You may write to us at support@icebox.com for any privacy concerns and requests relating to this Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.  

##### Call Now

##### More Pages

[Contact Us](https://www.icebox.com/contact) [Return & Exchange Policy](https://www.icebox.com/terms-and-conditions#term_20) [Frequently Asked Questions](https://www.icebox.com/faq/all) [Careers](https://www.icebox.com/careers) [Catalog](https://www.icebox.com/catalog) [Financing](https://www.icebox.com/financing) [Locations](https://www.icebox.com/locations) [About Us](https://www.icebox.com/about-us) [My Account](javascript:void(0);)

##### Shop By Products

##### Change Currency

 $ USD

3255 Peachtree Rd NE,  
Suite #2  
Atlanta, GA 30305, USA

Monday - Friday:  
11:00 AM - 6:00 PM

Weekends:  
Closed

##### Follow Us

Currency:

 $ USD

Icebox.com, 2024 ©. All Rights Reserved.

Explore Icebox

Men's

Women's

Gold Chains

Pendants

Earrings

Necklaces

Rings

Bracelets

Accessories

Travel Cases

#### Get notifications you will love with our free account!

Sign Up Now

Sign In To Your Account

Change Currency

##### Shopping Cart (0)

Your Cart Is EmptyAdd more diamonds to your life! [Start Shopping](https://www.icebox.com/)

#### Login to Icebox with OTP Enter your phone number and we'll send you a 4 digit code.

Phone Number

Send OTP Sign in with email

**Don't have an Icebox account?** Create Account

#### Login to Icebox with email Enter your email and password to sign in.

Email Address

Password

 Keep me signed in **Forgot Password?**

Sign In Sign In with OTP

**Don't have an Icebox account?** Create Account

#### Become an Icebox member Create your Icebox profile and get first access to the very best of Icebox products.

First Name

Last Name

Email Address

Phone Number

Password

 Male Female  Other

Create Account

 Sign up for emails to get updates from Icebox on products, offers, and your Member benefits

**Already have an Icebox account?** Sign In

Back To Login

#### Enter Verification Code We've sent the code to . Enter it below.

Submit Resend Code

#### Forgot Password? Enter your email address below, and if an account exists, we'll send you a link to reset your password.

Email Address

Reset Password Back to login

Something went wrong...

Change Currency
---------------

— Popular

USD  
United States Dollar

$

EUR  
Euro

€

GBP  
Pound Sterling

£

CAD  
Canadian Dollar

C$

AUD  
Australian Dollar

A$

JPY  
Japanese Yen

¥

— More

CNY  
Chinese Yuan

C¥

NGN  
Nigerian Naira

₦

ZAR  
South African Rand

R

PLN  
Polish Zloty

zł‎

MXN  
Mexican Peso

Mex$

SEK  
Swedish Krona

kr

DKK  
Danish Krone

kr

BRL  
Brazilian Real

R$

RUB  
Russian Ruble

₽

RON  
Romanian Leu

RON

CHF  
Swiss Franc

CHF

### Buy Now. Pay Later.  
No Fees.

Icebox.com is offering service through Klarna, Affirm or Afterpay.

Add items to your cart and get approved during the checkout process!

Approvals are fast and items are paid for instantly after your approval.

No Credit Score Impact Quick & Easy To Follow Personal Installments Plan

### How It Works:

Add items to cart and go through the checkout process

Click on the crypto payment type you would like to send.

Send the amount to the address in the checkout.

Send screenshot to us in Whatsapp to the phone number in the checkout, or by email to orders@icebox.com.

We will confirm we got the payment and communicate with you to make sure you get your order is completed.

Enter Your Email Address Your email is required to add to cart.

Email Address 

Add To Cart

STEP 1 OUT OF 3

Are you looking for a men's watch or ladies watch?
--------------------------------------------------

For Men

For Ladies

Are you looking for a watch with diamonds?
------------------------------------------

No Diamonds

With Diamonds

What metal do you like?
-----------------------

Two-Tone

Steel

Gold

All

Next

[LIVE

](https://www.icebox.com/chat-whatsapp)
